Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ankush-bohora-24b63978 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Product Design
Product Development
Additive Manufacturing

Certifications

SAP Certified Associate - Business Process Integration with SAP ERP 6.0 EhP6

Ankush Bohora

Mechanical Engineer Krefeld

Summary

I am working as a Product Engineer and Co-Founder of the German Tech-Startup 3D Innova Tech UG (haftungsbeschränkt), which specializes in innovative Engineering Solutions and focuses on international clients as well. With a bachelor's degree in Production Engineering from India and a German master's degree in Mechanical Engineering, I'm now passionately working in the field of Product Design and Development, and Additive Manufacturing / 3D-Printing.

Experience

3D innovaTech - Engineering Solutions Product Development Engineer August 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months) Greater Dusseldorf Area

Co-founder at 3D innovaTech - Engineering Solutions. Working in the fields of Research and Development, Product Design, Rapid Prototyping, and Additive Manufacturing / 3D Printing.

LIBERTY ACOUSTICS Design & Sound Product Management May 2019 - July 2019 (3 months) Greater Dusseldorf Area

Worked in the field of Market Research, Feasibility Studies, Interdisciplinary Teamwork, Business Model Creation, Project Supervision, Product Management, and conducting Workshops.

LIBERTY ACOUSTICS Design & Sound Product Design Engineer June 2018 - January 2019 (8 months) Greater Dusseldorf Area Master Thesis Project- Product design and lean product development. Design optimization and in-house prototyping using innovative 3D printing technology. Design for additive manufacturing.

Pegasys Systems Pvt. Ltd. Engineer Intern October 2012 - April 2013 (7 months) Mumbai Area, India

Design special purpose automated or semi-automated machines. Design optimization, automation, and control engineering in an environment of a small and medium-sized company.

Education

Rhine-Waal University

Master's Degree, Mechanical Engineering · (2014 - 2019)

Fr. Conceicao Rodrigues College Of Engineering Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Production · (2009 - 2013)